Hi, if you're looking for things to consider when you're rating a massage chair when you're thinking about buying one, I can give you a few things to consider and to think about before you make your purchase.
I'm Sundae with Natural Sundae.
Now there are about four things that you should really keep in mind when you're purchasing a chair, massage chair for massage.
What you want to do is you first want to think about the weight and how heavy it is.
You're going to be carrying it around and you don't really want it to, you don't want to hurt yourself carrying your chair around.
So you want to make sure it's fairly light.
You also want to make sure that it's fairly adjustable.
The headrest can move, this chest plate can move up and down, and there are definitely lots of movable parts on the chair.
You want to make sure that you know how to work your chair and that it's easy to work.
For instance, this chair is a little bit harder for me to set up.
It takes a few more minutes than a chair that's made a little bit better would.
Out of five stars, I'd probably give this chair a three.
So you want to make sure it's really easy to set up and that there's not too many moving parts.
The third thing to consider is the padding and there are many, most of the pieces on here are padded.
You've got your headrest which is really padded and that's really nice, you've got your chest plate, you see this one moves up and down, you've got your seat, you've got your leg guards and you've got your hand rest, your forearm rest.
So you want to make sure it's got enough padding for you.
And you also want to make sure it's comfortable to sit in.
You want to make sure it's really comfortable and some massage chairs just aren't comfortable at all and they look comfortable, so you just never know.
You want to sit in your chair definitely before you buy it.
So those are just four quick and very simple things to consider when considering which chair to buy for your chair massage.
I'm Sundae with Natural Sundae.
Take it easy guys.